(Ancient China, Ming Dynasty)
(Xuanhua pavilion)
Shi Qingyi: (opens the door)
Luo Shen, my new invention is ready.
Come over and take a look.
Shi Qingyi: Luo Shen?
Shi Qingyi: Hmm?
She is not in the house, where did she go?
(Shi Qingyi opens the door and goes out)
(Stream gurgling)
(Shi Qingyi arrive at the peach blossom tree)
(Luo Shen is sitting under the tree with her eyes closed.)
Shi Qingyi: How much wine has she drunk?
She just went and fell asleep under this tree.
Honestly.
Shi Qingyi: she didn't even put any clothes on
isn't she afraid of catching a cold?
she always makes me worry about her.
(Shi Qingyi covers Luo Shen with a robe.)
Luo Shen: (waking up and languidly and tipsily) Hmm?
Qingyi?
Shi Qingyi: (Gentle chiding) Is this wine so intoxicating?
How could you fall asleep here?
Luo Shen: The new wine you brewed for me
is quite delicious
I can't help drinking a little more
Shi Qingyi: You are so fond of wine
It's windy today
What if you catch a cold?
Hurry go back to your room if you want to sleep.
Luo Shen: What wind?
Why didn't I feel it?
I think it's very warm.
Shi Qingyi: It's warm? Are you drunk?
The peach blossoms have been scattered everywhere by the wind'.
Look at all the peach blossom petals on you.
And you still managed to sleep so soundly.
If you had gone to sleep,
I think you would have been drowned by the flowers.
Then I would have to dig you out of this petal pile.
Luo Shen: Didn't you just cover me with your robe?
Qingyi's robe can protect me
from even the strongest winds
Of course I can stay warm.
Shi Qingyi: You are the best at talking nonsense.
Shi Qingyi: (pouncing on Luo Shen) Give me back my robe.
Luo Shen: What for?
I was just warming up.
And now you want to take back the robe you covered me with?
Shi Qingyi: While the wind is strong.
I want to use this robe to catch some of the peach blossom petals
that have fallen and bring them back
(Luo Shen draws Shi Qingyi into her arms)
Shi Qingyi: Umm, you …… don't hold me so tight.
I won't be able to the peach blossoms.
Luo Shen: Well, Qingyi, you already smell good.
You don't need to bathe with these peach blossom petals.
Shi Qingyi: Who …… Who said I wanted to take a flower petal bath.
I'm just taking these to make wine.
Shi Qingyi:( lying on the top of Luo Shen and wriggling around) Let me collect these peach petals on you.
Don't move, don't let them fall on the ground.
Luo Shen: (indulgently) All right, I won't move.
(Shi Qingyi looks Luo Shen up and down.)
Luo Shen: You're collecting the petals on my body, aren't you?
Why are you looking at me like that again?
Shi Qingyi: You are pretty, that's why I'm looking at you.
Luo Shen: (light laugh) Such sweet words.
Shi Qingyi: Not as sweet as you, you old demon.
The words you said to me last night ……
Weren't they sweet enough?
I surrender.
Luo Shen: If I am an old demon, then what are you?
Shi Qingyi: I've been the wife of an old demon for so many years.
I suppose I just about count as an old demon as well.
Luo Shen: How many years have we been married?
Have you counted?
Shi Qingyi: From the Tang Dynasty to the Ming Dynasty.
That's a long, long time.
I don't want to count the years
That's too boring.
I've counted.
Shifu Qingyi: Why did you do that?
Luo Shen: I want to remember
all the time I've spent with you.
Every year, every day.
I don't want to forget a single monent.
Shi Qingyi:I don't want to forget either.
Luo Shen: Qingyi.
No matter how much the outside world changes
no matter how times change.
I will never, ever part with you.
Neither will I.
Luo Shen.
I will never part from you.
Shi Qingyi: Hyah!
The leader of the army in pursuit: Our superior has ordered the whole army to hunt her down.
Don't let her escape!
The chasing army: Yes!
Shi Qingyi: Hyah!
The leader of the pursuing army: Release the arrows! Force her off her horse!
Aim for the arms and legs, avoid the vitals!
Make sure to catch her alive, and there will give a big reward for you!
(Shi Qingyi dodges, grabs an incoming arrow, and flings it back.)
(The archer falls off his horse.)
(Shi Qingyi urges her horse into a gallop.)
(Modern-day, early morning)
(Shi Qingyi wakes up)
Shi Qingyi: Hmm… Why did I have that dream again,
I dreamt about that woman again.
Shi Qingyi: **Why I can never see her face clearly?**
**When I wake up, I can't remember her name.**
**I can't hear what she says very clearly either.**
**Who is she?**
TV Background Voice: Good morning,  everyone.
Today is Saturday, June 9, 2012.
Welcome to today's episode of The Morning News.
Here's ……
Shi Qingyi: Hey, Uncle Yang, good morning.
Have you eaten breakfast yet?
Uncle Yang: Yes, I've just eaten.
Shishi.
You're going to the Wuse store in Furong Lane today to get the goods from that guy Chen Jingfa.
When do you plan to head there?
I have to write my thesis in the morning, the professor is pushing me for it.
I'll go there at noon, still in time.
Uncle Yang: Okay.
You are now studying with Professor Yin Qing as a graduate student in the Department of Archaeology.
It's your third year of study, no wonder you're busy.
Still, your thesis is the most important thing.
Don't worry about the antique business over at Moyan Store,
You have me to take care of it.
Shi Qingyi: Thank you, uncle Yang.
Since I have you to help me with the store, I have nothing to worry about.
Uncle Yang: By the way.
Last time, Chen Jingfa took advantage of the fact that A Dong is a novice.
He switched an ancient inkstone with a fake one and give us the fake.
He thought we wouldn't know about it.
This time, since you're going to get the goods yourself.
We should knock some sense into his head.
Let him see how powerful Shi Qingyi, the Moyan Store can be.
Shi Qingyi: What power are you talking about?
Uncle Yang, you're making fun of me again.
Uncle Yang: hahaha.
Shi Qingyi: I will get it done
When I get the goods this afternoon, I'll bring them back immediately.
Uncle Yang, just wait for me at Moyan Store.
Jinjiang Literary City, original work by Jun sola.
Screenwriter: Jun sola
Producer: Baize Culture, BuZhiChan Studio, Jun sola
The audio drama "TanXuLing modern chapter".
Season One, Episode One.
The Beauty in the Tomb, welcome to listen.
(Wuse antique store)
Shi Qingyi: Boss Chen.
Please ask your guys to bring out the batch of goods ordered by uncle Yang.
I'll count them according to the list.
(The sound of a flute in the dark is faint.)
Chen Jingfa: A Cheng, go and bring the goods to Boss Shi.
A Cheng, why are you standing here?
Did you meet a ghost? why don't you go get the goods for Boss Shi?
A Cheng: Ah yes …… yes.
Sorry boss, I just got lost in thought.
I'll go now.
Chen Jingfa: Boss Shi, please wait a moment.
A Cheng will be back in a moment.
Shi Qingyi: Okay, there is no hurry.
A Cheng: Boss Shi, the goods are here.
There is one Qing Dynasty snuff bottle and
Two pieces of ancient lotus jade.
A piece of ancient sword frame of the Qing Dynasty.
There is also an orchid stone inkstone.
Please take a look.
Shi Qingyi: Thank you.
(Shi Qingyi examines the antiques.)
Shi Qingyi: Boss Chen.
Chen Jingfa: How about these goods?
Last time I just sent photos to Moyan Store.
This time is to see the real thing.
Do you feel satisfied with these goods?
Shi Qingyi: Everything is very good.
Chen Jingfa: **She even didn't notice this snuff bottle is a forgery**
**And said the stuff is very good?**
**With her poor eyesight.**
**How can she open Moyan Store and become the boss.**
Chen Jingfa: Boss Shi, your vision is beyond words.
These goods are all the best.
Shi Qingyi: Since Boss Chen said it is the best quality.
They must be the best.
The other three items are all good.
But recently, snuff bottles are not popular in the antique market.
The snuff bottles we bought in the store are not selling well.
I don't want this snuff bottle.
Chen Jingfa: This snuff bottle is the property of Shen Guangwen, a university scholar during the Qianlong period of the Qing Dynasty.
Boss Shi you are a connoisseur.
You should be able to see the value of this item.
Other snuff bottles do not sell well.
This one, how can it be not selling well?
Shi Qingyi: I know this is Shen Guangwen's stuff.
But this snuff bottle of the great scholar Shen.
Maybe the smell of snuff was too heavy in that year.
It's a bit strange.
I smell like glass and pine.
I don't like the smell, a smell of taint.
Chen Jingfa: **Now I know boss Shi is obviously a smiling fox.**
**She have already noticed it.**
**And she provokes me indirectly.**
**It seems that she noticed in the last batch of goods**
**The antique inkstone is faulty.**
**Now she's here to warn me.**
**I can't offend her again.**
**I'd better give her some benefits.**
Shi Qingyi: What? Boss Chen, you do not smell this smell?
Chen Jingfa: No …… did not smell.
Shi Qingyi: Oh yes.
The glass and pine are the raw material that will be mixed in the fake jade.
The top quality one in your hands
how can it be a forgery?
Right?
Chen Jingfa: Yes …… how can it be?
Boss Shi, that is impossible.
I do honest business.
I also believe in you.
But speaking of which.
The last time you sold us that ancient inkstone
It also has a different smell.
I don't really like that smell anyway.
Chen Jingfa: Since Boss Shi does not like the smell of the snuff bottle.
Then just take the remaining ones.
Speaking of which, Yang and I are old acquaintances.
But it's the first time I meet you.
First time meeting.
I shall give you a small gift today
as a favor.
All the antiques on the right shelf,
Boss Shi, if you like any of them.
just pick the one you like and take it back.
Shi Qingyi: You're very kind, Boss Chen.
(Shi Qingyi walks towards the antique shelf.)
(She saw a red jade bracelet.)
(Tanxuling original music: red jade bracelet)
Shi Qingyi: ** Strange, this red jade bracelet ……**
(She picks up the bracelet.)
Shi Qingyi: Then I'll pick this red jade bracelet.
I just saw it when I came in and I really like it.
Thank you for your kindness, Boss Chen.
Chen Jingfa: ** Didn't she have a very good judge of goods?**
**How come she chose a cheap one?**
**This red jade bracelet  was just bought from a farmer and cost me only a thousand dollars.**
Shi Qingyi: Yo, Boss Chen.
You're even happier than I was when I got the gift.
Chen Jingfa: No, no, no.
I am only happy that you are happy, Boss Shi.
This red jade bracelet is a genuine antique.
You really have a good sight.
Shi Qingyi: It is an antique, that's right.
I've already paid a deposit of 50,000 yuan a while ago.
The rest of the money, uncle Yang will pay to your card tomorrow.
Chen Jingfa: Yes, thank you, Boss Shi.
Let's have pleasant cooperation later.
Shi Qingyi: In fact, cooperation is pleasant or not.
The main thing depends on you, Boss Chen.
I've always been very pleasant.
Shi Qingyi: Boss Chen, then I'll go back first.
Goodbye.
Chen Jingfa: Okay, take care.
Hey, the little fox is quite difficult to deal with.
(Shi Qingyi returns to the car and puts the goods away.)
(She took out the red jade bracelet and put it on.)
(TanXuLing original soundtrack: red jade bracelet)
Shi Qingyi: (examining the bracelet) this red jade bracelet ……
Is really interesting.
Shi Qingyi: Hmm?
Ning Ning: Don't move.
Shi Qingyi: You…
Ning Ning: (Lowered voice) Don't turn back yet.
Do as I say.
Otherwise, I'll shoot you.
Shi Qingyi: **I can't afford to mess with her.**
**I have to delay with her as long as possible.**
Shi Qingyi: I… I'm a good citizen.
Even if you don't point a gun at me.
I will …… obey and not move around.
Ning Ning: Good citizen?
You have watched too much television?
I don't watch much TV.
I usually spend more time on the computer.
Ning Ning: Shut up
Shi Qingyi: This section of the road has electronic surveillance.
You're holding a gun, don't mess around.
Everything will be captured.
Ning Ning: I am wearing a mask, the gun is also covered.
I'm not afraid of electronic surveillance.
Shi Qingyi:  I don't have much cash on me, and I don't have my card with me.
If you want a car, then
I give the car keys to you, you drive away.
Please don't hurt me.
Ning Ning: I don't want cash, I don't want cards
and I don't want your car either.
I want the red jade bracelet on your hand.
Shi Qingyi: I'll take the bracelet off and give it to you right away.
Ning Ning: Don't move. You can't take it off.
Shi Qingyi: What?
Shi Qingyi: **How could this happen?**
Ning Ning: Don't toss and turn.
I just told you.
After you put it on, you can not take it off.
To take it off.
Unless you become a dead person.
Or.
Cut off the hand that you wear the bracelet.
Shi Qingyi: So.
Do you want to kill me?
Or are you going to cut off my hand?
Ning Ning: Neither.
This red jade bracelet is not yet able to touch blood.
I want you to come with me.
I can go with you.
As long as you don't hurt me.
Can I ask you a few questions?
I don't understand
what you're doing to me right now.
Ning Ning:  Ask more, die earlier.
Shi Qingyi: I'm not asking any more questions, then.
Just can you let me tie my shoelaces?
The laces are a little loose.
Ning Ning: Why do you a good citizen has so many things to do?
Go ahead, hurry.
(Shi Qingyi ties her shoelaces and puts down a small object.)
Shi Qingyi: It's okay, thanks.
Ning Ning: Behave yourself and go.
Shi Qingyi: **I hope uncle Yang can see what I left on the side of the car when I was tying my shoelaces.**
**Know that something happened to me and go to find me.**
Ning Ning: Get in the car.
Ye Zhen: Hi, big beauty, how are you?
Shi Qingyi: Hello
Your sunglasses are very handsome.
Ye Zhen: Sister Ning, this beauty is really nice.
Very interesting.
We've kidnapped her.
But it looks like she's not afraid of us at all.
Gutsy.
Ning Ning: Behave yourself.
Nice guy, but not yours.
Ye Zhen: Hey, sister Ning, look what you said.
This lady, you are not lucky.
Today our boss will have to use this ghost chain on your hand.
**Ghost chains?**
We looked for a long time before.
Finally heard that it was sold to a man named Chen Jingfa in Furong Lane.
Today we were going to Chen Jingfa's Wuse store to get the goods.
But unfortunately, you wear it at first.
This is fate.
Ye Zhen: But don't worry, ghost chains are contraindicated by blood.
We will not cut off your hand.
to avoid staining with blood.
You just need to obediently follow us.
Shi Qingyi: Will I die?
Ye Zhen: Miss, you ask me such a professional question.
I'm not sure how I can answer you.
Shi Qingyi: You are a professional about that, aren't you?
You have a pistol and a short-handled saber hanging on your belt.
It's not for show, right?
Ye Zhen: Miss, what is your name?
You are gutsy, I like you very much.
Shi Qingyi: My name is Shi Qingyi.
Ye Zhen: Miss Shi, I'm Ye Zhen.
This is Ning Ning, the one who brought you here.
We all call her Sister Ning.
We're going to the boss's place to meet up with him.
There are also a few brothers.
Also, I tell you.
Although I am a professional.
Since I joined this business.
I have never killed a woman.
So I should feel lucky that
You have never killed a woman.
Ye Zhen: Haha.
Ning Ning: Ye, every time you meet a beautiful woman.
Would you die if you say a few words less?
Don't forget what you do for a living.
Why waste words with her.
Hurry up and tape up your beautiful girl's mouth.
Then seal your own mouth.
Ye Zhen: (Makes a gesture of sealing his mouth with his hand) Okay, Sister Ning.
All sealed up, quiet.
(SUV starts)
(The Falling Goose Mountain)
(Shi Qingyi, Ning Ning, Ye Zhen get out of the car)
Ye Zhen: (kindly remind) Miss Shi, we are now at the Falling Goose Mountain
The car just climbed the mountain road and it was very bumpy, you have no motion sickness, right?
Shi Qingyi: Thank you Mr.Ye, no.
Ning Ning: (annoyed) Ye Zhen, are you out of your mind?
Why did you tell her that this is the Falling Goose Mountain?
Do you afraid she doesn't know where she is when she's been kidnapped? right?
Why don't you tell her all your ancestors?
Ye Zhen: Haha sister Ning, do not be angry.
Look at my stupid mouth.
Ning Ning: Fuck you.
Ye Zhen: (quietly) Miss Shi.
Sister Ning is just a little mean-mouthed.
Let her scold and it will be fine.
Don't be nervous.
Shi Qingyi: I'm not nervous.
(Shi Qingyi is walking in the forest.)
Shi Qingyi: Hmm?
The man A: How come they go out for so long?
I'm tired of waiting.
When can we get down to the tomb?
And see what treasures there are inside the tomb.
Man B: Hey, it's Ning and Ye Zhen, they're back.
Shi Qingyi: **they actually dug a robber hole here?**
**It turns out that Ning Ning and Ye Zhen and their group.**
**Is to do this kind of tomb robbery business.**
**Their profession and my major in archaeology are the opposite of each other.**
**I must not let them see that I know the stuff in tombs.**
Ning Ning: Brother Dong, it's done.
Dong Jun: Ning Ning, what happened to this woman you brought back.
I told you to go to Chen Jingfa's place to get the ghost chain.
Why bring me back a woman?
Ning Ning: originally we went to get the ghost chain.
But I was a step late.
She snatched it and wear it first.
You also know the ghost chain ……
Dong Jun: I know the ghost chain can not get blood.
No need to cut her hands, feed her some medicine to eat.
When poisoned, the blood clogged in the body, and
Will not flow to the ghost chain.
When her body is cold.
Then take off the ghost chain from her corpse.
Shu Qingyi: **…… calm.**
Ning Ning: Brother Dong, now only she can open the door at the bottom.
We can't let her die yet.
Dong Jun: I forgot about that.
Since she is wearing the ghost chain.
Then hurry up and take this woman down.
Dong Jun: Get up, all of you.
Get up, don't dawdle.
Let's go down the hole.
Shi Qingyi: **When I am not useful**
**I'm sure they'll kill me.**
**I have to think of countermeasures quickly.**
Shi Qingyi: **But they all have guns on them ……**
**I have to take my time.**
Dong Jun: Go down.
Ning Ning: (cold eyes at Shi Qingyi) Shi, you go down first.
I'm on guard, don't think about playing tricks.
Shi Qingyi: I see.*
Ye Zhen: Miss Shi, this cave is very difficult for ordinary people to enter.
Let me carry you down.
Shi Qingyi: No, you help me block her sight.
Ye Zhen: Oh?
Shi Qingyi: Do not let Ning Ning see me.
Ye Zhen: Okay.
(Shi Qingyi along the rope, lightly leap down the cave.)
(Ye Zhen comes down from above along the rope)
Ye Zhen: (whispering in surprise) I can't believe it.
Miss Shi, you have kung fu?
You're so good at going down the hole and flipping the rope.
You seem to be better than even us.
What exactly do you do?
Shifu Qingyi: Don't talk nonsense.
Even if I know kung fu and can flip ropes
It's not as powerful as real bullets.
You give me a shot, I will immediately die.
Ye Zhen: (smiling) Don't worry, I can't let you die.
I will not say anything.
Ning Ning: (urge from back) hurry up and go, what are you muttering at front.
(Shi Qingyi and others go down along the tomb passage deeper and deeper)
(TanXuLing Original soundtrack: Down the tomb)
Shi Qingyi: **What they want to open is this door?**
Dong Jun: Ning Ning, you let the woman to the front of the door.
Ning Ning: Shi, what are you dawdling for?
Come over and open the door.
See the 18 round holes above the door?
Each one is matched with your hand ghost chain outline.
You put your hand into the middle of the hole so that the ghost chain can be stuck.
Did you hear what I said? Ah?
Shi Qingyi: Yes.
(Shi Qingyi walks to the door and rubs the engraved letters on the door.)
Shifu Qingyi: (reads the words engraved on the door) Only when the master of the Ghost Chain has come.
This door will be opened.
The chains can't get blood and cannot be defiled.
Shi Qingyi: So it is.
The words carved on this door is to say that the master of the Ghost Chain must be alive.
No wonder just now ……
Ning Ning: Since you know, cut the fucking crap.
The Mater of the Ghost Chain, open the door.
Shi Qingyi: The mechanism hole is so deep.
I don't know what's waiting for me inside.
If I go in rashly.
will I lose my hands?
Shi Qingyi: **hands are so important.**
Ning Ning: what are you dawdling for?
Shi Qingyi:  **No idea.**
**life is more important than a hand.**
(Shi Qingyi puts her hand into the doorway)
(mechanism opens)
(tomb door opens)
Ye Zhen: (elated) Hey, it's open.
This ghost chain really lives up to its name.
Quickly, the chamber behind the door is finally ready to enter.
(All step into the tomb)
Zhan Fei: Why is there nothing in this chamber?
Only some broken chains.
Ning Ning: Zhan Fei, look over there.
Take a good look at these chains.
All gathered in the white jade platform over there.
Zhan Fei: Good God, there is a crystal coffin on that white jade platform!
Wealthy, wealthy!
Sister Ning has good eyesight.
This is really a coffin to make a fortune!
Shu Qingyi: **Lying in the crystal coffin it's seemingly a woman?**
Ye Zhen (be on guard) watch out, there is a zongzi in that crystal coffin!
Shi Qingyi (in a trance): This is ……
Ye Zhen: (alarmed, stopping Shi Qingyi) Miss Shi, you do not know these,
Don't go there first, that's a zongzi!
Like these bodies lying in the coffin of the tomb is called zongzi.
Once they have absorbed the breath of the living.
they will probably become active.
Sit up from the coffin.
And attack people!
Only to use black donkey's hoof, the ward off evil things that restrain the dumplings specifically
and put it into the mouth of the zongzi.
The zongzi can no longer attack people!
Sister Ning, get the black donkey's hoof out!
Ning Ning: I'll take it when you tell me to?
Who are you, Ye?
Dong Jun: I have a gun in my hand, why do I need black donkey's trotters?
Eat for yourself?
Get your weapon ready, go forward to see.
the existence of zongzi is a good news
You know that the zongzi carries valuable treasures.
Get a piece of them, we will make a lot of money.
(Dong Jun approaches the crystal coffin)
Dong Jun: looks like there are no signs of the zongzi becoming active
Open the coffin.
Others: Yes
(Open the coffin)
Shu Qingyi: (saw the appearance of the woman in the coffin, overlapping sound) this woman ……
Ye Zhen: (awe) my goodness, am I dizzying?
This …… zongzi in this coffin looks too ……
too beautiful!
Shi Qingyi: **what's going on?**
**Why do I want to touch the woman in this coffin?**
Luo Shen: every year, every day in the past,
The time I spent with you, I want to remember.
Every moment, I do not want to forget.
I don't want to forget either.
Luo Shen: Qingyi.
No matter how the dynasties change outside, how time goes.
I will never, ever part with you.
Shi Qingyi: Neither will I.
Luo Shen.
I will never be separated from you.
Ye Zhen: There is a vermilion dot on her eyebrow.
Her left hand is missing a little finger hey?
Ning Ning: This person is dead, what do you care what she is missing.
Ye Zhen: such a superb beauty.
It's a pity that she's missing her little finger.
Shi Qingyi: (in a trance) …… what's going on.
Ye Zhen: Miss Shi, Miss Shi, are you okay?
Shi Qingyi: (back to her senses) no …… nothing.
Ye Zhen: Miss Shi, don't be afraid.
She is just a dead person.
To put it bluntly, it's just a zongzi.
Look at her
She won't get up to attack you.
Dong Jun: Zhan Fei, you go over there.
See what goodies that zongzi is carrying.
Zhan Fei: Okay, Brother Dong.
Zhan Fei: Look at the woman in the coffin, the skin is watery.
So beautiful ……
Damn, I've never seen such a good-looking person in my life.
I did not expect her to become a zongzi
What a fucking waste.
Ning Ning: (cynical and poisonous) Zhan Fei, no matter how beautiful she is
It's not your turn to feel sorry for the waste, huh?
Look at your behavior.
Dong Jun: Cut the crap.
People are dead, what can be the point.
Don't dawdle.
Hurry up and strip her clothes.
These clothes have not decayed for so many years.
It must be worth a lot of money.
And see if there are any other treasures on her body.
Get it all off.
The corpse is not decomposing.
Either it was filled with medicine.
Or there are face-keep pearls in her mouth.
Take them all out.
Zhan Fei: I'm coming.
Let me search this beauty's body.
Shi Qingyi: (coldly) Take your dirty hands away.
Zhan Fei: (furious) What do you mean?
Dare You say it again?
Shi Qingyi: (suppressing anger) I said, take your dirty hands away.
You have no right to touch her.
Zhan Fei: You're fucking tired of living, aren't you?
I'll shoot ……ouch!
Shi Qingyi: Do not move!
Zhan Fei: (panic) you …… you calm down.
This gun is not a joke!
Dong Jun: That's really unexpected.
You pretended to be weak all the way
Hide your ability.
You even know kung fu!
Shi Qingyi: If you guys dare to move, I'll kill him immediately!
Ye Zhen: (nervous) Miss Shi.
Zhan Fei: Boss, brothers, don't move.
Do not move!
Dong Jun: Shi, Zhan Fei is just a cheap life.
Do you think you can threaten me?
(Dong Jun fires, hitting Zhan Fei's leg.)
Zhan Fei: (screams) Ahhh!
Zhan Fei: Dong Jun, you cold-blooded beast, I'll fuck your whole family!
Dong Jun: Shi, did you see?
Since I was able to cripple Zhan Fei's leg with this shot.
In the next shot, I will be able to blow your head off.
Since you know we are here to robe tomb.
I will definitely not let you go out alive.
Otherwise, if you leak messages later.
I will have to take responsibility.
(Shi Qingyi throws Zhan Fei away, Zhan Fei falls to the ground)
Shi Qingyi: I knew it already.
In front of you desperadoes.
No matter what I do, I will due finally.
(Shi Qingyi walked over to the crystal coffin and gazed at the woman in the coffin.)
Dong Jun: Seeing that you are so nervous about the woman in the coffin.
If you die next to her.
You shouldn't be too sad, right?
Ye Zhen: Boss, I beg you, please don't kill her.
I promise Miss Shi will never tell others.
Dong Jun: Your guarantee is a ghost.
The mouth is on her face.
If she is alive
she wouldn't have spilled the beans about this today?
I think she is not a simple person.
She knows kung fu.
And so disobedient.
How dare she threaten me?
How can you guarantee?
Ye Zhen: Dong ……
Dong Jun: Shut up.
(chains shaking)
Man A: boss, boss, look!
Man B: Boss, look at the woman in the coffin, she …… she ……
Dong Jun: shout what shout, did you see the ghost?
Ning Ning (shivering): Brother Dong, got up, she got up, you ……
Dong Jun: What up?
Ning Ning, why are you making a fuss too?
Shi Qingyi: (surprised)
Original Soundtrack of Tan Xu Ling: "Luo Shen"
Shi Qingyi: **There is no embroidery in the green pines**
**But there is an exiled goddess in the human world**
**Is this the kind of person the poem is talking about?**
**How can there be ……**
**Such a good-looking person in this world**
Luo Shen: You are really noisy
Dong: Ahhhhhh the zongzi is getting up!
Shi Qingyi: Watch out!
(Luo Shen holds Shi Qingyi in her arms)
Luo Shen: You ……
Qingyi?
Shi Qingyi: Don't …… don't just stand there!
They have guns!
Luo Shen: Hmm? Guns?
(Bullets fly towards them, Luo Shen dodges swiftly, kicking the attackers aside)
Dong: Ah!
(Machinery works)
Ning Ning: **What's going on?**
**Brother Dong was kicked and landed on the mechanism of the tomb door.**
**Now the door will close soon, I have to get out of here!**
**A group of good-for-nothings.**
Luo Shen: Qingyi! I'll heal your wounds.
Shi Qingyi: Go!
The tomb door …… The tomb door is about to close
If the tomb door is closed, we can't …… go back the same way
Luo Shen: Qingyi!
Ye Zhen: Miss Shi, go quickly!
Qingyi, don't be afraid, I'll take you out of here!
(Using qinggong to fly up, Luo Shen carries Qingyi away)
Ye Zhen: She didn't even use the nylon rope, she just flew up!
Grandpa and Grandma, this ……
Is this white-clothed zongzi using the legendary qinggong?
Stepping on snow without a trace! Ling Bo Wei Bu!
The wuxia novels are true!
(Stones roll down, tomb door closes)
(Falling Goose Mountain)
Luo Shen: Qingyi, Qingyi
Shi Qingyi: Hmmm……
Luo Shen: …… I have to get this dart out as soon as possible.
Shi Qingyi：No …… it hurts ……
Luo Shen: Good girl, calm down
This dart is so powerful that it is extremely dangerous to leave it in your body
We need to use a dagger to remove it
Qingyi, bear with it for a while
Shi Qingyi: You …… I ……
Shi Qingyi: Mmmmm ……
Luo Shen: Qingyi, I'm going to take out the dart for you
Shi Qingyi: Mmmmm!
(Luo Shen uses a dagger to cut a strip of white cloth from her robes to bandage Shi Qingyi)
Shi Qingyi：You…… who are you?
Luo Shen: …… Did you
forget me again?
Shi Qingyi: Of course I recognize you!
You are ……
You are the ancient zongzi
who woke up in the crystal coffin in the tomb just now
Luo Shen: Silly girl, I'm not a zongzi
I'm your wife
Shi Qingyi: …… wife?
I'm a woman.
How can I have a …… wife?
Luo Shen: (stunned) Qingyi, you ……
Shi Qingyi：Water, I’m so …… thirsty.
Luo Shen：All right, you stay here for a while
I am going to fetch water, I will be back soon
Don't be afraid, wait for me.
(Luo Shen leaves, using qinggong.)
Shi Qingyi: Ummm……
Music Producer/Produced by: Jun sola
Lyrics: Jun sola
Luo Shen: Qingyi
I am
Performed by: 少司命@少司命-Jessi
your Wife
Composer/Arranger/Mixer: willen@猫先生willen
Flute Recording: 囚牛@笛呆子囚牛
Shi Qingyi: This woman, why do I feel like she's trying to grope me
I can't forgive this kind of hooliganism
just because she's an ancient
Luo Shen: My name is
Luo Shen
Do you remember?
Don't forget
♪Lyric♪
Translator: zhufree & douqi