(Hospital ward)
(Shi Qingyi is unconscious and pants gently)
Nurse: Mr. Yang, Miss Shi Qingyi is in stable condition now,
The doctor said she should wake up soon,
You don't have to worry too much.
Lao Yang: Okay, thank you, nurse.
Luo Shen: Qingyi.
Luo Shen: Qingyi,
I'm your wife.
Shi Qingyi: Hmm... hmmm.
(Shi Qingyi wakes up)
Lao Yang: Shishi!
Shi Qingyi: ...Uncle Yang.
Lao Yang: Thanks to the old ancestors for their blessings.
You've been sleeping for a day and a night, you're finally awake!
Shi Qingyi: Umm....
I have been...... (Lao Yang: Shishi, slow down.)
sleeping for a day and a night?
Lao Yang: I'll raise the head of the bed up for you.
Shi Qingyi: Thank you, uncle Yang.
Lao Yang: Don't worry,
the doctor has operated on you.
There's nothing seriously wrong.
But you've lost too much blood, you need more rest.
Lao Yang: Come, have some water.
Shi Qingyi: Ok.
Shi Qingyi: (remembered something) **......?**
**Water...**
**Oh wait ......**
**I was rescued from the ancient tomb by the woman in white**
**who got up from the crystal coffin.**
Luo Shen: Don't be afraid. I'll take you out of here.
**The woman said she was going to find me water to drink…**
Luo Shen: You stay here for a while.
I'll go to get water and will be back soon.
**Now I am in the hospital being cared for.**
**What about that woman?**
**Now thinking about it, she is definitely not a zongzi,**
**but a living person.**
**After all, when I was held in her arms,**
**I can feel her warmth and breath**
**What's more, she can also speak.**
(Luo Shen: Don't be afraid, Luo Shen: Wait for me)
**Hundreds of years are like one day in the ancient tomb**
**She…**
**She should be an ancient person**
**who suddenly came to modern times.**(Lao Yang: Shishi?)
Lao Yang: Shishi.
Shi Qingyi: (in a trance) Ah?
Lao Yang: What are you thinking about?
You've been staring into space for so long.
You've nearly finished the water, but you are still drinking.
Shi Qingyi: I... just got a little distracted.
Uncle Yang, please put the cup away for me.
Lao Yang: Ok, I'll peel an apple for you as a snack,
then go out and buy some porridge later.
Shi Qingyi: (thinking) **Can an ordinary person**
**live in an ancient tomb for so many years?**
**Why didn't time leave**
**any traces on her?**
Lao Yang: Ah, what porridge would you like?
Shi Qingyi: Anything light will do.
By the way, uncle Yang,
Is there any person in the world
who is able to sleep for hundreds of years
without eating or drinking.
And then wake up again
still looking like before?
Lao Yang: Shishi, why are you suddenly asking me about this?
Shi Qingyi: You know, I like these strange things,
I want to know more.
I heard that there is a kind of water lily with a very hard seed shell,
the seeds lie buried in the mud,
and need to be dormant for a long time.
After a few hundred years,
the dormancy of water lily seeds finally ends and
the flowers bloom again.
And this flower is from several hundred years ago.
Do you think there is any possibility of humans doing the same?
Lao Yang: If I tell you, it is very likely,
Will you believe it?
Shi Qingyi: Tell me more?
Lao Yang: The effect of drugs.
Or the art of tortoise breath.
Shi Qingyi: (becoming interested) Oh?
Lao Yang: In fact, in ancient times, the art of alchemy was prevalent.
There were all kinds of magical elixirs,
and numerous secret evil arts, curses, poisons.
That level of magic
is not what we modern urbanites can understand.
Shi Qingyi: ... Secret arts.
Lao Yang: Yes
Most of these things
have been lost.
Even if a small number of them were handed down,
they have been kept secret.
People now,
in fact, know only a drop in the ocean
about the thoughts, behaviors and secrets of the ancients.
Shi Qingyi: That's true,
I also think ancient people are very mysterious.
Lao Yang: For example, the question you just asked,
I think if a person can take some kind of pill,
or use a secret art such as turtle breath,
The body's metabolism will stop
in a state of deep sleep.
But as long as there is a big stimulus from the outside world,
Or the drugs or secret arts lose their effectiveness,
This person will wake up again,
their Physical functions will be restored,
And they will become a normal person.
Shi Qingyi: In other words, when such a person falls into her deep sleep,
Time stops for her, doesn't it?
Uncle Yang: Yes.
Shi Qingyi: (Thinking) **I see... Interesting.**
Shi Qingyi: By the way, uncle Yang,
who brought me to the hospital?
Lao Yang: Some mountain climbers saw you in a coma at Luoyan mountain,
And took you to the hospital.
Shi Qingyi: (worried)**The woman went to find water for me,**
**What if she doesn't see me when she comes back?**
Lao Yang: Fortunately, you have your mobile phone on you. The last call in the mobile phone is for me,
I got a call from the hospital and came right away.
Lao Yang: Come, eat some apple.
Shi Qingyi: Ok.
Lao Yang: Speaking of it,
The doctor said you were shot in the shoulder,
But the bullet has been removed,
And a simple bandage was wrapped around your wound.
But how did you get shot for no reason?
Shi Qingyi: Huh? It's raining.
Oh, I was kidnapped and brought to Luoyan mountain on the outskirts of the city,
In the confusion, I was shot.
Lao Yang: You said you were kidnapped,
Which bastard in Changsha did it?
Who dares to touch a member of the Shi family?
Do they want to die?
Shi Qingyi: I don't know,
I didn't even see what they looked like. Let it go.
Shi Qingyi: **It's too complicated,**
**The secret is probably very deep,**
**Don't let uncle Yang worry.**
**And if uncle Yang knows**
**He will definitely tell…**
**Shi Yeran.**
Lao Yang: You don't know. I was worried to death before.
You went out for so long in the afternoon and didn't come back,
You didn't answer your mobile phone or your home phone,
I just felt that something was wrong.
Then I found Furong lane,
I saw your car parked there,
And this thing had fallen beside the tire.
Here, put it away.
Shi Qingyi: Luckily you found it.
Lao Yang: Fortunately, the ring is small
so no one saw it and picked it up.
I remember this ring was a birthday present from your aunt when she was still alive,
You like it so much,
I'm sure you wouldn't have left it lying around,
And I was right, something really did happen.
Shi Qingyi: It happened suddenly. I was also taking a gamble.
Because the ring my aunt gave me is very valuable,
I left it as a sign.
Others don't know, but uncle Yang you can recognize it.
I was hoping no one else would pick it up,
In fact, I was very reluctant to leave it.
Lao Yang: It is fine now that you have the ring back.
You just woke up, you need more rest,
I won't talk to you too much,
The police will come to you to take a statement.
Shi Qingyi: Uncle Yang, I know what to say to the police,
But don't go after the people who kidnapped me,
I don't want to make this a big deal.
Don't say I was shot,
Just say I accidentally fell and went to the hospital.
Lao Yang: But boss Shi…
Shi Qingyi: (cold) Especially don't tell Shi Yeran.
Lao Yang: ... OK.
Shi Qingyi: Uncle Yang, I want to leave the hospital today.
Lao Yang: I see,
I'll find an excuse to help you transfer hospitals,
You can go home and rest.
Your body is unusual,
You'll recover from even this gunshot wound quickly,
The doctors really shouldn't find out.
Shi Qingyi: Thank you, uncle Yang.
Lao Yang: By the way, Shishi, I almost forgot to give this to you.
Shi Qingyi: (surprised) This is …
Lao Yang: This is the bandage that the doctor removed from your shoulder before,
Others can't tell it. They think it's an ordinary rag,
But you know what you and I do.
Shi Qingyi: Yes, I see.
This is the best mercerized brocade,
It was only produced in the early Ming Dynasty,
At that time, only the royal family and nobles or the very rich in the city could afford to wear this.
Unfortunately, this craft has disappeared.
Mercerized brocade doesn't decay. It's very valuable,
At present, in the antique industry,
This kind of thing is a great treasure.
Luo Shen: Qingyi, I'm going to pull out the concealed weapon
Lao Yang: Shishi,
It's amazing that someone used this mercerized brocade,
which can be called a treasure in the antique industry, to bandages your wound,
I've lived to such an old age,
But I couldn't have imagined it.
Shi Qingyi: I'll put this white cloth away.
I know what to do,
Uncle Yang, don't worry.
Shi Qingyi: **The woman in white,**
**Is she from the Ming Dynasty?**
Jinjiang literature City, the original work of Jun sola,
Screenwriter: Jun sola
Producer: Baize Culture, BuZhiChan Studio, Jun sola
Audio drama "TanXuLing modern chapter",
Season one, Episode Two,
What's your name?
Welcome to listen.
(Congested Street)
Radio Hostess: We just received a call from a concerned citizen,
At present, Jianshe Road is suddenly blocked by traffic for some unknown reason,
Please detour to pass Jianshe Road as far as possible to avoid congestion
Passerby: What happened? It's blocked like this,
Is it a serial crash or a rear end!
Passerby: Can it be faster? I'm in a hurry!
Shi Qingyi: It seems that the traffic jam will last for a long time.
(Shi Qingyi takes out the brocade box containing white cloth strips)
Shi Qingyi: This cloth strip
wait,
Why am I looking at the white cloth that the woman in the ancient tomb used to bandage me,
How many times have I done it already,
Is there something… wrong with me?
Is she from the Ming Dynasty?
It's so interesting.
I don't know if I'll see her again.
Traffic policeman A: Please give way, give way.
Please spread out and cooperate with us. Don't get stuck on the road
Traffic policeman B: Well, miss,
Please don't stand in the middle of the road like a piece of wood!
Shi Qingyi: (Curious) Huh?
Passerby: What are they looking at?
So strange? I thought a fairy must have come down to earth.
Passerby: I don't know. Anyway, it's blocked like anything,
And the cars can't move. Let's go and have a look.
Passerby: This woman looks so beautiful, isn't she a movie star?
Why is she walking around dressed like this?
Passerby: What's the fuss,
Hanfu, ancient clothes and so on are very popular now,
I see people go to work dressed in hanfu these days.
Passerby: Is she making a movie?
Passerby: It looks like she just escaped from a film set .
Shi Qingyi: **Star? Filming? Mental hospital?**
(Traffic policeman B: Miss, you didn't know to avoid the car before It's dangerous.)
**What a mess this is.**
Passerby: She isn't speaking, she's just looking at the traffic policeman,
How can the traffic policeman tolerate it,
Shi Qingyi: Excuse me.
Shi Qingyi: (Stunned) **This,**
**The person blocking the road is**
**The woman in white in the coffin?**
**Am I dreaming?**
**Am I Really... Seeing her again?**
Traffic policeman B: I said, miss, do you have facial paralysis or are you mute?
Luo Shen: (Confused, mumbling) Facial paralysis?
Traffic policeman B: ...Er.
Passerby: The little traffic policeman blushed under her gaze again.
Luo Shen: Huh?
Luo Shen: (Surprise) **Qingyi?**
Shi Qingyi: (Nervous) **Did she look at me?**
Passerby: This woman is beautiful and strange,
Take a picture of her and post it on weibo. That certainly can earn you some kudos.
Shi Qingyi: No photographs. She's my relative. Would you please respect her privacy?
Passerby: Ah? Your relative.
Do you have a beauty gene in your family?
Shi Qingyi: Sorry, comrade traffic police, this is my cousin.
She just escaped fromthe municipal psychiatric hospital,
Her brain doesn't work properly,
And she likes role playing.
Comrade traffic police, don't blame her,
I'll take my cousin back home right away.
Traffic policeman B: Psychosis? Cosplay?
Take her back home quickly,
Look, what's the jam like?
I won't issue a ticket. Take her away,
I'm going to evacuate the road.
Take care of your cousin from now on,
Don't let her run wild,
What a strange thing.
Shi Qingyi: Don't worry, comrade traffic police. I'll take my cousin home right away.
Traffic policeman B: Change her clothes quickly,
Dressed like this, she's out of place.
It's not a filming set.
Shi Qingyi: **if I tell you,**
**She is a Ming Dynasty woman who woke up in an ancient tomb,**
**You'll be scared to death.**
Traffic policeman B: Stop watching the fun. There is nothing to see!
Shi Qingyi: Cousin,
Come on, come home with me.
Luo Shen: Yes.
(Roadside)
Shi Qingyi: Well... Let's stop at the roadside first.
Shi Qingyi: We drove all the way here in my car,
Are you feeling well? Are you carsick?
Luo Shen: **Car?**
Shi Qingyi: Do you know what a car means?
Luo Shen: (Seriously) You said this four-wheel box made of iron armor,
Is called a car?
It's different from carriages
Shi Qingyi: Ah?
Yeah, yeah, that's what I call a car.
Shi Qingyi: (Funny) Four wheel box?
What a lovely way you describe it
Luo Shen: Lovely?
Shi Qingyi: I mean... it's interesting
Shi Qingyi: Well, look,
What do you think these two are?
Luo Shen: **this…**
**Everything has changed, only…**
**Only the appearance of Qingyi has not changed.**
**But she clearly doesn't remember me,**
**She's even testing me with these.**
Shi Qingyi: You...
Shi Qingyi: **Did she find that I'm testing her?**
**I really shouldn't tease her so much.**
Shi Qingyi: The one that makes a sound is the car horn,
This is the gear lever.
You... It doesn't matter if you don't know,
I'll tell you later.
Luo Shen: Yes.
Luo Shen: (a little gentle) Is your wound healed?
Shi Qingyi: (stunned) Huh?
Shi Qingyi: Do you think I'm strange?
I was injured two days ago. Now I can walk and run.
Luo Shen: You're not strange.
Shi Qingyi: *Why does it seem that she knows my special skill of rapid recovery?
**Is it an illusion?**
Luo Shen: That day you were hurt ,
I went to get you some water to drink,
When I came back, I found you missing.
Shi Qingyi: Sorry,
when you went to look for water,
I was discovered by another group of people,
I was out of my mind and couldn't leave you a message,
and was sent directly down from the mountain for treatment.
Luo Shen: So,
It's good that you were all right.
Shi Qingyi: Thank you for helping me then.
Luo Shen: You don't have to thank me.
Shi Qingyi: It's hot today, are you thirsty?
Luo Shen: Yes
Shi Qingyi: Let me undo your seat belt first,
You wait for me in the car and I'll buy some beverages.
Luo Shen: What do you mean by beverages?
Shi Qingyi: Beverages are what you drink.
Luo Shen: Is it like wine?
Shi Qingyi: wine is a kind of beverage.
Beverages include wine, but wine does not represent all drinks,
It includes other varieties.
Luo Shen: Yes.
Shi Qingyi: Wait for me here. I'll be back soon.
Luo Shen: (Whispering) Qingyi.
Shi Qingyi: Shopkeeper, please give me two bottles of coke, chilled.
Boss: Here you are.
Shi Qingyi: Thank you.
Shi Qingyi: (Thinking as she walk) **These modern things should be very strange to this Ming Dynasty woman,**
**But she didn't seem confused or afraid,**
**She's also subconsciously learning.**
Shi Qingyi: **She has strong adaptability,**
**She is definitely not a simple character.**
**I have to find a chance to get to know more about her.**
Shi Qingyi: I'm back.
Here you are, coke.
(Luo Shen drinks coke and frowns)
Luo Shen: (Unhappy) Cousin, it tastes bad.
Shi Qingyi: (Almost spits out a mouthful of coke) You…
Why do you call me cousin?
Luo Shen: Just now in front of that noisy freak,
Didn't you say I was your cousin?
You said there was something wrong with my brain,
Did I hear wrong?
Shi Qingyi: ...Er.
Luo Shen: (Chuckles)
Shi Qingyi: Don't take it seriously,
If I don't say you're a psychotic,
The traffic police won't let you go,
Maybe they'll take you to the Public Security Bureau.
Public Security Bureau, in your Dynasty,
It's equivalent to the yamen, which handles criminal cases.
Luo Shen: You said our Dynasty.
So, you know I'm not from your dynasty?
Shi Qingyi: Wait, let me grab something.
(Shi Qingyi takes out the brocade box)
Shi Qingyi: (Seriously) I'm a graduate student majoring in archaeology,
And I run an antique shop,
Therefore, I have a certain understanding of historical antiques.
This white cloth is yours.
I recognized the cloth as mercerized brocade, right?
Luo Shen: Yes.
And mercerized brocade was only produced in the Ming Dynasty,
The craft was lost later.
And,
A few days ago, you sat up in the crystal coffin of in the ancient tomb on Luoyan mountain ,
I thought you were a zongzi,
Then I realised you were a living human.
If I'm not mistaken,
You must be
Someone from the Ming Dynasty.
Luo Shen: You are still so clever,
and lovely.
Shi Qingyi: Thank you for your praise,
I'm just basing this on the information I have
And the evidence in front of me.
You're welcome.
Luo Shen: Are you not afraid of me?
If others know that I came from an ancient tomb,
They must regard me as a monster and avoid me.
But you,
You brought me here and talked to me.
Shi Qingyi: Why should I be afraid of you?
You saved me. You must be a good person.
I'm not an ungrateful person,
You saved me so I'll help you.
Luo Shen: I'm fine. I don't need help.
Shi Qingyi: Don't be angry. I don't mean anything else,
I am a good citizen, please believe me.
You are now in this strange environment,
There are many things that you won't understand if no one teaches you,
That's why I said I would help you.
Luo Shen: Yes.
Shi Qingyi: By the way, I was just focused on talking to you
I still don't know your name yet.
(Original soundtrack of Tan Xuling: Ask your name)
Shi Qingyi: my name is Shi Qingyi. What's your name?
Luo Shen: (Unhappy) You said you are Shi Qingyi,
Why don't you know my name?
Shi Qingyi: (Confused) My name is Shi Qingyi,
My family gave it to me.
What does it have to do with whether I know your name?
Luo Shen: (Dejected) My name is Luo Shen.
Remember it, don't forget it.
Shi Qingyi: **The Goddes of Luoshui?**
**What a unique name.**
Shi Qingyi: Luoshen, it's a rare name,
Of course I won't forget. I'll remember it.
Luo Shen: (Lost) Okay.
That's good.
Shi Qingyi: (Inexplicably distressed) **I asked her name,**
**Why does she look …**
**A little sad?**
Luo Shen: Miss Shi.
Why did you bring me here,
And said you wanted to help me,
Just now, you also helped me avoid prison.
You and I don't know each other,
And my identity is very special,
You are so kind to me,
But what's your intention?
Shi Qingyi: I won't beat around the bush with you.
I do have an ulterior motive,
But it's not malicious. Don't worry.
Well…
I'm interested in you.
Luo Shen: Huh?
Interested… in me?
Shi Qingyi: I... I didn't mean that. Don't get me wrong.
I... I don't have that inclination.
Luo Shen: (Sneers)
Really? No such inclination.
Shi Qingyi: Did I say something that makes you unhappy?
Luo Shen: No
Shi Qingyi: Well... I have something to discuss with you.
Luo Shen: What?
I am now preparing a crucial research topic,
For my graduate thesis.
Luo Shen: Topic?
This so-called topic is equivalent to
It's equivalent to the essays that students wrote to the emperor
for imperial examination in the Ming Dynasty, so it is very important.
Whether you can get the favor and appreciation of the emperor,
Depends on that essay.
Do you understand me?
Luo Shen: Yes.
On this subject,
I've chosen
"local customs and political culture
About the cultural relics unearthed in the Ming Dynasty".
Therefore, I hope you can help me complete this research topic.
Shi Qingyi: **she... Why is she keeping silent again?**
Shi Qingyi: It's just... I want to hire you as my archaeological data provider,
I'd like to ask you for help and provide detailed cultural and local information about your Dynasty.
Of course, as a thank-you, I'll pay you a salary,
Salary means wages, which means silver.
At the same time, I'll provide you with life consulting services in this era,
So that you can understand and adapt to this strange world as soon as possible.
Miss Luo, this is a win-win situation,
I hope you can consider accepting my offer.
Shi Qingyi: **What a good deal.**
**Even if you're a piece of wood,**
**It's time to nod your head.**
**(Continuous silence)**
**What a piece of wood,**
**No, she's an iceberg with facial paralysis.**
**I just said so much,**
**Why isn't she saying a word,**
**Didn't give me even a look.**
Shi Qingyi: Miss Luo,
Do you understand me?
Luo Shen: Yes.
Shi Qingyi: Are you willing to promise?
Luo Shen: I want to take a bath.
Shi Qingyi: What?
Luo Shen: I'm so dirty,
Excuse me, miss Shi, where can I bathe?
Shi Qingyi: I'll take you to the bathing place.
Luo Shen: Thanks a lot.
Shi Qingyi: It's time to drive, you're probably still not used to it
Let me fasten it for you, ok?
Luo Shen: Yes.
Shi Qingyi: (Gently  telling) In modern society,
Traffic rules must be observed,
This seat belt must be fastened.
You see, that's it.
Luo Shen: (Sighs)
Shi Qingyi: (Take a deep cold breath) What?
**Why did she**
**Suddenly put her hand on my shoulder?**
**Her hands are... so cold.**
Shi Qingyi: Miss Luo,
You... Your hand,
Can you put it down?
Luo Shen: You're pressing against my body like this,
I don't know where to put my hand.
Shi Qingyi: **You don't know where to put your hand,**
**Is it comfortable for you to put it on my shoulder?**
Shi Qingyi: I... I didn't mean to press against you,
It's... Because I need to help you fasten your seat belt,
I have to lean over.
Luo Shen: Yes.
Put it down.
Shi Qingyi: **This woman,**
**Why do I feel that she's groping me**
**Not only does she not obey the traffic laws,**
**But also taking advantage of me?**
**I can't  forgive such…**
**Outrageous behavior…**
**Just because she's an ancient…**
Luo Shen: Miss Shi.
Shi Qingyi: What?
Luo Shen: Don't you want to take me somewhere where I can take a bath?
Shi Qingyi: Er, yes, let's go now.
Luo Shen: (Chuckles) **Qingyi.**
**It doesn't matter if you don't remember me.**
**I'll let you know me again.**
(Shi Qingyi's home)
Shi Qingyi: Miss Luo, this is where I live,
Do as you like, Miss Luo.
Luo Shen:Okay.
Luo Shen: (A little relieved)
**Fortunately, there are only Qingyi's shoes here.**
Shi Qingyi: Wear these slippers. They are new.
Luo Shen: You live alone?
Shi Qingyi: How did you discover this?
Luo Shen: (Flickering smile) Miss Shi,
You seem quite familiar with the ancient tongue
Shi Qingyi: I mean, how did you find out?
Luo Shen: There are not many shoes here,
And all of them fit your size, so I guessed.
Shi Qingyi: You can tell the size of my shoes at a glance?
Luo Shen: (Whispering) I know all your sizes.
Shi Qingyi: (Goes farther) What? What did you just say?
Luo Shen: Nothing.
Shi Qingyi: Miss Luo, sit down please.
Luo Shen: Yes.
(Shi Qingyi prepares various drinks)
Shi Qingyi: (Excited) **I can't believe it,**
**I brought home an ancient woman from the tomb,**
**A woman belonging to the Ming Dynasty.**
**As long as Luo Shen agrees to cooperate with me,**
**I can get so much precious historical information from her.**
**This is living history.**
**I have to coax her.**
Shi Qingyi: (Smiling) You must be thirsty. Have a drink.
What kind do you like?
I don't know your tastes. You choose it yourself,
I think you may not be used to carbonated drinks,
So I didn't get that for you.
Luoshen: Just milk.
Shi Qingyi: Milk?
What did milk taste like in your Ming Dynasty?
What's the difference between then and now?
Shi Qingyi: **In ancient times,**
**Only the upper class or well-off people can afford milk,**
**It seems that she must have been very rich in the Ming Dynasty.**
Luo Shen: I want another drink.
Shi Qingyi: (Interrupted) What?
Luo Shen: Milk.
Shi Qingyi: Oh, OK, wait a minute. I'll pour it for you.
Shi Qingyi: **Does she like milk so much?**
**She even wants two glasses.**
Shi Qingyi: Miss Luo, here is the milk.
Luo Shen: You drink.
Shi Qingyi: Ah?
Luo Shen: Don't you like milk?
This one is for you.
Shi Qingyi: **Strange**
How did she know I like milk, too?
Luo Shen: Don't you like it?
Shi Qingyi: I like it
Luo Shen: The question you asked me about the milk just now
I'll answer you now
Shifu Qingyi: Yes, okay.
Luo Shen: During the Ming Dynasty, milk had a heavy fishy smell
and a faint smell of rawness
But your milk here is different, it has a mild taste
but it does also have a distinctive
tasty flavour
Shi Qingyi: (smiles gently)
Luo Shen: Why are you looking at me like that?
Shifu Qingyi: I think you are very special
Luo Shen: Is that so? Why am I special?
Shifu Qingyi: Miss Luo, I think you are very interesting
Luo Shen: Oh?
Shifu Qingyi: If I were a Ming dynasty person and I woke up from a dream and walked out of a tomb
And saw that everything was different outside, I would have felt panic and anxiety in my heart.
But you are different, you don't seem to care
Luo Shen: It's very common for dynasties to change.
It's just a law of creation.
As history progresses, dynasties change
The outside world is also changing rapidly
I'm used to it, it's no big deal
Even though I might be in the harshness of the sand dunes
Or snowy mountains
Or in one of your new dynasties
I don't think there's anything wrong with that
If I don't understand what's around me,
I'll learn, until I understand it, and I'll get used to it
Even if the outside world changes, people have to live.
There's no need to panic
Shi Qingyi: You're really different from ordinary people, that's why I think you're special
But you just said "I'm used to seeing it"?
I don't know if my understanding is biased
What you said, it seems mean ......
You've been through a lot of dynasties changing, haven't you?
Luo Shen: You didn't misunderstand.
I have been through the change of dynasties often
From the Warring States to the Tang Dynasty to the Ming Dynasty
Almost two thousand years.
This kind of dynastic change
I've seen a lot of it and I'm used to it
But what do you expect?
Shi Qingyi: Miss Luo, I can't believe you ......
You're also quite good at telling jokes
**You’re not immortal**
**How can you have lived through the Warring States, the Tang Dynasty and the Ming Dynasty?**
**You've experienced all the changes of the dynasties**
**Itmust be just a joke**
Luo Shen: I was indeed telling a joke
Qing ......
Miss Shi, did you like it?
Shi Qingyi: I thought you were from the Ming Dynasty
I didn't expect you to cross over from the Warring States to the Ming Dynasty
Chinese history is only about 5,000 years old
You've taken up almost 2,000 years, almost half of it
I really admire ......
Luo Shen: Do you think I'm not clear-headed and talking nonsense?
Of course I don't
I'm not three years old, would I believe you, the queen of groan worthy jokes?
And you say you're over 2,000 years old, are you an old spirit?
(Luo Shen laughs gently and presses Shi Qingyi onto the sofa)
Shi Qingyi: Huh?...... you ...... you
Luo Shen: (gazing at Shi Qingyi, breathing up and down)
Shi Qingyi : **She ...... she just suddenly pinned me to the sofa**
**What the hell does she want to do?**
The original soundtrack of Tan Xu Ling: Seeing Luo
(Shi Qingyi tries to push Luo Shen away gently)
Luo Shen: (pushed lightly by Shi Qingyi, holding back a slight gasp)
Shi Qingyi: (torn) **Hey, should I ...... push her away?**
**It seems ...... like it's not very polite**
**But she pinning me down like this, she ...... is not polite either**
**She ...... smells so good**
**No, I ...... what am I thinking about?**
Shi Qingyi: What do you want to do, I am a good citizen
Miss Luo, I hope you can learn from me too
Be a good citizen
Luo Shen: (smiles meaningfully)
Shi Qingyi: (nervous)
Luo Shen: I don't want to do anything
I just remembered I should bathe
Good citizen Miss Shi
Shifu Qingyi: ...... Yes?
(Luo Shen gets up from the sofa)
Shi Qingyi: (puzzled) Why is this person so odd sometimes
The original soundtrack of Tanxuling: Qingxuan
Shi Qingyi: The bathroom is over there, I'll take you there
Luo Shen: Hmm.
(Luo Shen looks at Shi Qingyi's back and laughs lightly)
Music Producer/Produced by: Jun Sola
Composed by: Zhangyue Lu Li @盏月陆离
Arranger: Luojack @洛劫
Mixer: willen@猫先生willen
♪Lyric♪
Shi Qingyi: I didn't expect her to take the initiative so quickly
Why does it feel like she's a hunter?
And I'm like the prey she's after?
Luo Shen: It seems that Miss Shi has studied my subject here
and already done a lot of research
Next time, do you want to study somewhere else?
Lyrics by: junsola@君sola
Singer/vocalist:龟娘@龟仙人龟娘
♪Lyric♪