Lyrics: Mo Hu Qiang Wei
Composer: Mo Hu Qiang Wei
Arrangement/Vocal Harmony: Gong Xun
Vocals: Yun Zi (Nangong Jingnv), Qi You (Qi Yan)
Mixing: Liu Jialun
Jingnv: You, are the initial intention, the eternity
the deep sea, the raging fire
the devotion, the illusion
Me, I wavered in thought, made mistakes
quenched my thirst, fell into the devil's grasp
planted the seed, tasted the fruit
Qi Yan: You, in the temple hall, by the pillow
at the crossroads, in my heart
before my eyes, on the horizon
Me, difficult to break free, difficult to linger
difficult to hate, difficult to forgive
difficult to choose, difficult to have it all
Heart, already shattered long ago
Vanishing into ashes
Since entering the dead end, it's hard to regret after hundreds turns
Jingnv: Love, falling into a tear
I don't blame anyone
But myself, for giving my true love to the wrong person in the end
Qi Yan: Path, without looking forward, without looking back
without hesitation, without turning back
without calculating, without letting go
Jingnv: Sigh, a battle, a pain, a love, a dream, a play, a void
Together: Heart, already shattered long ago
Vanishing into ashes
Since entering the dead end, it's hard to regret after hundreds turns
Love, falling into a tear
I don't blame anyone
But myself, for giving my true love to the wrong person in the end
Qi Yan: Heart, already shattered long ago
Vanishing into ashes
Since entering the dead end, it's hard to regret after hundreds turns
Jingnv: Love, falling into a tear
I don't blame anyone
But myself, for giving my true love to the wrong person in the end
Together: Heart (heart), already shattered long ago
Vanishing into ashes
Since entering the dead end, it's hard to regret after hundreds turns
Love (love), Love, falling into a tear
I don't blame anyone
But myself, for giving my true love to the wrong person in the end
Jingnv: In the next life, let's continue our predestined relationship and return to each other